

Eryk Kucharski

Nationality: Polish

(+48) 729246100

Date of birth: 11/09/2002

Gender: Male

■ Email address: erykkucharski.ek@gmail.com

Email address: eryk_kucharski@tlen.pl

Website: <u>ehoze.github.io</u>

Whatsapp Messenger: +48 729 246 100

f Facebook: <u>fb.com/ehoze</u>

• Address: ul. Wiejska 32A, 63-520 Książenice (Poland)

ABOUT ME

For several years I have been actively learning various programming languages and I want to develop in this profession. I am constantly trying to improve my skills and competencies required in this occupation. I can easily communicate in English. I have at least basic knowledge of many programming languages. I adapt to a group of people, so working in a team is not a problem. I believe that everything can be learned and I have no fear of learning anything new. I am a fast learner and at a dynamic pace I am able to move from learning to using something already in and for work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Webmaster

Grupa Tense Polska Sp. z o.o. Sp.k. [01/02/2022 - Current]

City: Wolsztyńska 5, 60-361 Poznań

Country: Poland

My duties included optimizing websites for SEO and implementing various, interesting changes on clients websites. In 90% of the pages I worked on PHP, HTML and CSS sometimes also JavaScript. With the rest I learned SMARTY language and many, many different CMS, from Wordpress through Prestashop, Shoper to more niche ones like Idosell or Goldshop. In terms of tasks I had frequent contact with

co-workers from other departments so I practiced teamwork and gained experience of how it looks like to work as a team.

Intern/Trainee

MikroB S.A. Zakład elementów i systemów automatyki przemysłowej [01/05/2021 – 31/05/2021]

City: Ostrzeszów Country: Poland

The aim of the internship was to acquire new and improve existing competencies and practical skills. My tasks were:

- > Learning the software "SCADA PRO-2000" system to supervise the course of a technological or production process.
- > Learning basic definitions of industrial automation.
- > Learning and testing applications on the Open62541 library the equivalent of OPC-UA library.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Specialty: Programming Technician

Zespół Szkół Nr 2 im. Przyjaźni Polsko-Norweskiej [01/09/2018 - Current]

Address: Krańcowa 7, 63-500 Ostrzeszów (Poland)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Polish

Other language(s):

English German

LISTENING C1 READING C1 WRITING B2 LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B2 SPOKEN INTERACTION B2 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A2 SPOKEN INTERACTION A2

DIGITAL SKILLS

HTML / CSS / JavaScript / PHP / Laravel / React / C++ / Java / Frontend / Backend / CMS - Wordpress, PrestaShop, Shoper / Github / SQL

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

How i love to spend my free time

Rozmowy z ludźmi, spacery, bieganie, siatkówka, programowanie, technologia komputerowa, mechatronika, elektryka. Spotykanie się ze znajomymi, dalekie podróże nocą i spontaniczne wypady.

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: AM 11/2021

Driving Licence: A1

Driving Licence: B1 11/2021 **Driving Licence:** B 11/2021